Guide to the Cornell University diploma and certificate collection, 1876-1948.
Cornell University diploma and certificate collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University diploma and certificate collection, 1876-1948.
37-5-2637
Cornell University.
1.5 cubic feet
Diplomas and certificates.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection consists primarily of Cornell diplomas from alumni, but also includes some Cornell certificates and non-Cornell certificates/diplomas from alumni.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection consists primarily of Cornell diplomas from alumni, but also includes some Cornell certificates and non-Cornell certificates/diplomas from alumni.
Also, some empty mailing tubes and the bottom piece of a February 8, 1922 diploma.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.
Form and Genre Terms:
Certificates.; Diplomas.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Cornell diplomas
Series II. Certificates and non-Cornell items from alumni
Series III. Mailing tubes
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Cornell diplomas
  - Behringer, George Frederick: Bachelor of Arts, 1869
    This item is in the Behringer papers, collection #37-5-242
  - Brewer, Carolum Temple: Baccalaurei in Philosophia, 1876 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Knowles, John Moulton: Bachelor of Science, 1873 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cornell, Oliver Hazard Perry, 1874 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Purdy, Markwell Seward: Bachelor of Science, 1882 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dix, Charles Billings: Mechanical Engineer, 1888 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bliss, Johannem Carleton: Bachelor of Arts, 1889 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Washburn, Albert Henry: Baccalaurei in Philosophia, 1889 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Kuhn, Joseph: Mechanical Engineer, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Goodenough, Myrta Lillian: Bachelor of Arts, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Petty, Alfred Smith: Bachelor of Arts, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Morrison, Olive Butler: Bachelor of Arts, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Davis, Cortland Woodbury: Mechanical Engineer, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Parker, Esther Emily: Doctor of Medicine, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ritter, Frederick William: Bachelor of Arts, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Abbott, Clinton Seth: Mechanical Engineer, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Hooey, William Charles: Bachelor of Chemistry, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sayre, Henry Denton: Bachelor of Laws, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Parker, Clarence Douglas: Bachelor of Arts, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Card, Wendell Thomas: Bachelor of Science, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Berkowits, Hyman: Bachelor of Arts, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Berkowits, Hyman: Master of Arts, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Brown, Camilla June: Bachelor of Science, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Gilkey, Gladys Fay: Bachelor of Arts, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Griffin, Edna Mae: Bachelor of Science, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Hays, Charles Hodge, Jr.: Mechanical Engineer, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mouronval, Alice Emma Louise: Bachelor of Arts, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Nathan, Miriam: Bachelor of Arts, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Berkowits, Hyman: Doctor of Philosophy, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ovenshine, Eugene Samuel: Civil engineer, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Robbins, Gertrude: Bachelor of Arts, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Juravleff, Feodosy Alexander: Bachelor of Science, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sailer, Paul Allison: Civil Engineer, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Vreeland, Glenna Robbins: Bachelor of Arts, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Christner, Paul William: Bachelor of Science, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Pape, John Herman, Jr.: Bachelor of Arts, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Payton, Jerome: Doctor of Veterinary Medicine, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Warren, Marie Garner: Bachelor of Arts, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Trafzer, Thomas C.: Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Series II. Certificates and non-Cornell items from alumni
  - Card, Wendell Thomas: High School Diploma, Troy Public Schools, Pennsylvania, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Berkowits, Hyman: College Entrance Diploma in Arts, University Scholarship Certificate, Brooklyn Scholar, diploma from El Museo Canario, 1913-1951 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Trafzer, Thomas C: Ensign in Navy certificate, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Parker, Esther Emily: license to practice medicine and surgery from University of the State of New York, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Series III. Mailing tubes
  - Empty mailing tube for Glenna R. Vreeland's diploma, Undated; MU-1375 (Box 1)
  - Empty mailing tube for Clarence Parker's diploma, Undated; MU-1797 (Box 1)